Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Until someone proves it real.
Through it all.
Through all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
So I can know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend.
We are.
We are on the cruise.
We are those three.
Think they can mock me?
Screw that.
I consider this act of
aggression a declaration of war.
There you are, Mohji.
I hope you wouldn't mind if I
take the pirate hunter's head.
Be my guest.
What's with this dog?
Doggy!
Zoro, it looks like this dog is frozen.
I don't give a damn, he could
sit there forever for all I care.
I wonder if it's dead.
Luffy, please, quit goofing
around and get serious.
Damn dog.
I don't feel good.
Oh, hi, Navigator.
I guess you can have this.
You got me out of a
pretty sticky situation.
Great, the key to the cage.
Did you go steal it for me?
Thanks, Nami.
They only did it so we'd be even.
Yeah, sure.
Stupid, stupid, stupid dog!
Hey, stop that?
Stop picking on poor Chouchou!
Leave him alone.
Who might you be, old man?
Old man, why, I'm the mayor of this town Who
are you and why are you hurting Chouchou?
How's Zoro?
I told him he really should see a doctor.
But he insisted that he didn't need to!
and just wanted to sleep it off.
So this dog's name is Chouchou?
Why is he just sitting there like that?
He sure is a lazy dog.
He's guarding the store.
Huh?
Oh, I see.
It's a pet food shop.
That's right.
And the man who used to run this
store was a very close friend of mine.
There you go.
When he passed, I assume the
responsibility of taking care of Chouchou.
He died?
Yes.
Three months ago, after fighting
his illness for a very long time.
Don't tell me he's been waiting for
his master to return all this time.
That seems to be the consensus.
Huh.
But I find that very hard to believe.
Chouchou is a smart dog.
He's probably known for a while
that his master isn't coming back.
Then why does he stay here at the store?
I guess because he has a connection to it.
It's his treasure.
He's guarding it.
His master left him with this shop,
and that's why he protects it.
I've tried to bring him back to my place
so he won't be out in the elements,
but he won't take so much
as a step away from here.
What's that sound?
It's him!
Beast Tamer-Moji!
We gotta go! Run!
What do you mean by Beast Tamer?
Wait, hold on!
Come on, puppy, something's here.
Why don't you just give me that key back?
I see that your friends have deserted
you, and after you just escaped.
Who the heck are you?
I'm known as the Beast Tamer-Moji,
a member of the Buggy Pirates.
Whoa, that's a weird
animal suit you got on.
That was rude.
This is manly hair.
Okay, that's even weirder.
You shouldn't assume that you're safe
just because you're in that cage.
You must not know of my terrifying skill.
There is no animal in this world that Beast
Tame Emoji can't bend to do his bidding.
Shake.
Why does it hurt so bad?
You nameless thief, I've
no interest in killing you,
but tell me where Roronoa Zoro
is before I change my mind.
No way!
Ritchie, attack!
Yes, I'm finally out!
Nice work.
Good boy, Ritchie.
Now let's go find Zoro so I can defeat
him and strengthen my reputation.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's a pet food store.
Make it quick, then.
Let's go.
Don't tell me this pathetic little thing
really thinks he can guard the shop.
That was intense.
At least now I'm out of that cage.
First thing, I teach those
buggy pirates a lesson,
and then I convince Nami to
be the navigator for my crew.
Huh?
How did you survive that attack?
You're alive?
I just got lucky, I guess.
Surviving an attack
like that isn't normal.
I figured you'd be scattered all over.
It's not normal.
Why exactly did you decide
to come to this town?
And how'd you get involved
with those pirates?
All I'm doing is searching
for a chart of the Grand
Line and a good navigator
to join my pirate crew.
I think that guy in the animal suit said
he was looking for Zoro, so I gotta go.
Chouchou, this shop belongs
to the two of us now.
That bag is way too big for you, Chouchou.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha...
Be careful, Chouchou.
Don't hurt yourself.
Leave this to me.
Pat Chouchou, I told you
not to eat the merchandise.
Now let's chow down!
Well, not ready to give up yet.
Chouchou, I'm getting on in years now.
I gotta go see the doctor for a checkup.
But I'll be back, so guard
the shop until I return.
I'm counting on you, Chouchou.
Hold down the fort.
He has a connection to it.
It's his treasure.
He's guarding it.
His master left him with this shop
and that's why he protects it.
Dammit, I can't believe that
annoying little dog bit me.
Wait, I thought I killed you.
What are you still doing alive?
I'm afraid you can't get
rid of me that easily.
This time, Crush's head
into the ground, Richie!
I'm not gonna be beaten by a lion!
Gum-Gum!
Hammer!
What are you?
Well, I ate the Gum-Gum Devil Fruit.
So then you have Devil Fruit powers like
Captain Buggy, but yours make you rubber?
Sorry!
I apologize for attacking!
I don't want any trouble!
There's no reason for
you to apologize to me.
Because of you, that dog will
never get his treasure back.
And now, because of that,
I'm going to kick your ass.
Pirates are all the same.
They're all just a bunch
of heartless bastards.
They destroy everything that people hold
dear without giving it a second thought.
Oh, you're alive, pirate! You know,
I thought for sure that lion was going
to tear your head off and end it all.
And I wish he had, because then there'd
be one less pirate in the world!
Maybe I should kill you
right now before you
can gather a crew and
destroy everything else!
Come now.
There's no need for violence.
As if you could ever kill me.
Well, maybe I'll try it and see!
I said stop!
What's with you people?
Sorry, but that's all I could say for you.
That bastard lion ate all the rest of it.
He...
he fought the lion in order
to save the dog's food?
You fought well.
Of course, I didn't actually
see you defend the store,
but I can tell you gave it your all.
Thanks!
Good luck to you, too, doggy!
You were defeated? How?
I'm very sorry, Captain.
Sorry, I failed.
Moji, I can't believe you
were defeated by Zoro.
No, it wasn't Zoro.
It was that Straw Hat.
What?
There's no way that skinny little punk
could have gotten the better of you.
He's eating the gum.
Now I'm really pissed off.
All right, prepare all the
remaining special buggy balls.
I'm gonna blow this entire
miserable town to smithereens.
Sorry about earlier I
didn't mean to yell at
you that's okay you've
been under a lot of stress
lately but hey no need
to apologize I'm pathetic
shu shu and this young one
have fought so hard and
yet I the mayor have
done nothing but sit back
and watch our town be
obliterated by buggy and his
despicable crew calm
down it's not that bad 40
years ago this whole area was
nothing but Barren, rugged land.
We all work together to
create fields for our crops.
We opened stores and built
everything from the ground up.
This town is a treasure to
me and all its citizens.
From here on out, I refuse to let Buggy
and his crew terrorize us anymore!
Fire a special, Buggy Ball.
Blow this town away!
He'll destroy it all.
Zoro was sleeping in there!
I'm sure he's dead now.
Zoro, you in there?
Are you still alive?
That's one hell of a way to wake a guy up.
I could have used a few more Zs.
How did you survive that blast?
Oh, right! You're alive!
I refuse to let him get away with this.
I won't stand for it.
I can't let this scumbag destroy all of my
townspeople worked for
these last 40 years.
I am the mayor of this town.
I will protect it and its inhabitants.
I swear to my dying breath. Stop!
You can't defeat Buggy!
Perhaps, but there are some
fights that a man can't run from.
Isn't that right?
That's right, old man.
Shut up!
Don't egg him on, Luffy.
It's dangerous for him to fight Back.
I know it's dangerous!
I'm coming for you, Back the Clown!
The mayor was crying. He was?
I didn't notice.
Looks like the party's
getting more exciting.
Sure does.
This is no time for laughter.
Don't worry, I started to
grow fond of that old man.
There's no way I'd let him die.
Well, in that case...
You're gonna go too?
You're wounded!
Yeah, so what?
The injury to my reputation's a lot
worse than the injury to my gut.
Well, if we want to get to the grand
line, we better go steal that chart back.
Ha!
Are you gonna join our crew or what?
Huh? Come on!
I'll never sink so low
as to become a pirate.
But I suppose we could team up in
order to achieve our common goal?
Second shot is ready sir.
All right, then fire
I'm mayor Battle in
this town is my treasure
I won't let you terrorize
my people any longer.
So come out and fight me you
idiot This town is no treasure.
Treasure is gold, silver, and jewelry.
So cut the crap, old man, and get
out of here before I kill you.
You can never understand how I feel!
Soon I'm going to conquer the Grand Line
and flashily obtain all the world's riches.
And there's nothing you can do to stop me.
All the world would belong to me.
Now, if this town means so much to you,
then perhaps I'll do you a
favor and kill you first.
That way you won't have to see
me destroy your precious village.
Shut up!
And fight me already!
Don't get cocky.
I'll never let you destroy this
town, if it costs me my very life!
So be it.
That Straw Hat's not again!
I'm here to kick your ass, just
like I promised I would, Buggy.
How dare you!
You can't just waltz up to
me and treat me like this!
I'm Captain Buggy and
I won't stand for it!
Listen to me, all I want is
the chart and the treasure,
then I'm out of here, you got it?
Yeah, I got it.
Get out of here.
Why'd you follow me?
You're outsiders, leave this to me!
This is my fight that I need to
be the one to protect my town.
Buggy is my fight!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Why'd you knock out the mayor?
Because...
That's not a bad idea.
As the old man had continued
to fight, he would have died.
That's for the best.
You didn't have to hit him!
I'm sure I could have thought of a more
humane way to deal with the situation!
That's the worst thing you
could have said to him!
Oh, you damn flashy idiot!
I won't stand for this!
Take aim and fire the Buckyball!
Why'd you have to say that?
Come on, Luffy, we gotta go.
You go ahead.
Time to die!
I'm fine, just watch.
Bum, bum, bum!
What is he?
Did he catch the Buckyball?
Run for us!
He could have warned me.
All right, I got him!
What the hell kind of monster are you?
I think you freaked her out.
I knew that something was weird after
you survived the fight with that lion!
No human being can do what
you do Now explain yourself,
what the hell was the balloon
inflatey thing that you did just now?
That was the Gum-Gum balloon.
I don't care what you call it,
just tell me how you did it!
What are you, some kind of freak?
How dare you try to flashily do me in!
Unreal, using his men as a shield.
Hm?
What in the world just happened here?
No! It's you!
Ah, it's that damn Straw Hat!
Captain Buggy, we have to be careful.
He has Devil Fruit powers too.
He's a rubber person.
I saw it myself. What?
Rubber person? Yeah.
A Devil Fruit.
That explains how he bounced
that buggy ball back to us.
How do you plan to respond
to this insult, Captain?
Oh, Kappa G.
I don't know.
I'm too angry to even fart.
Put him down, Kappa G.
What the hell did you do to my Ritchie?
This cat?
I used it as a shield to keep
my clothes from getting dirty.
Ritchie!
No, Ritchie!
Say something, please!
Ritchie!
Damn you!
You bastard!
Out of my way!
How about out of my way?
You may call me Acrobat Copper Team,
Captain Buggy's chief of staff.
You will pay for your insolence.
I'll clash swords with you.
It's an honor, Roronoa Zoro.
As a swordsman myself, I
relish this chance to slay you.
Hey, Zoro, you really
should get some rest.
Let me handle this guy.
Just stay back.
That's the stab wound the captain
inflicted on him, the fool.
Harsinus, technique!
Ah!
What's wrong?
I didn't kick you that hard enough, did I?
He fights dirty, going
after his injury like that.
Acrobat technique?
Murder at the steam bath.
Acrobat, my ass.
That's just an ordinary dust cloud.
He did it again!
What's this?
It's such a disgraceful sight
to see a grown man moaning.
I suppose now you can see how foolish it
was to make an enemy of the buggy pirates.
He's hurt so bad, I don't know how
he's managing to stay in the fight.
Why are you just standing
there watching him?
He's gonna get himself killed, you know?
Roranoa's Zoro is finished!
You annoying little bastard.
You having fun poking in my wound?
Then go ahead!
Ouchie!
Why didn't you dodge his attack?
Is that enough of a handicap for you?
And now let me show you just how
superior my skills are to yours
You've made a vast error in judgment.
I won't be mocked my swords aim
to be the world's greatest I
Refuse to lose even once to anyone
who calls himself a swordsman.
I see
A strong resolve keeps you going.
But have no fear.
Wounds as bad as yours will be
more than enough of an excuse.
For losing to me.
To hell with that.
If I lose to someone like you,
even with these minimal injuries,
then I don't have a very bright
future ahead of me, do I?
Why, you...
All right, yeah! Yeah!
I won't stay and watch this.
You pirates can stand around for the rest
of time and kill each
other for all I care.
I mean, it doesn't matter to me
whether you guys win or lose.
I'm gonna take this opportunity to swipe
their treasure and get out of here.
Maybe we can team up again
if we ever get the chance.
See ya, good luck with the fight.
Yeah, thanks, see ya!
Here's a taste of my
ultimate acrobatic move.
Acrobat technique, the dance
of a hundred kamikaze times.
Acrobat technique, a
hike in the mountains.
Fireworks in the cool summer breeze.
Whoa, that's high.
Sting of the unicycle.
Ground hugging, chop chop colonel.
Kamaji, I'll hold him.
Then you finish him off. Duh.
Damn it.
Luffy.
You bastard.
If you want to fight
someone, how about me?
I assure you, I don't need my
captain's help to finish you off.
Enough.
I'm tired of this.
So you've finally given up, have you?
I must say,
I'm quite impressed that you lasted
that long with such serious injuries.
I think you misunderstood.
I'm tired of watching your
boring little sideshow.
So sorry to have disappointed you.
How about my real swordsman skills?
Die, Zoro!
Rain!
Giddy!
Comedy!
I can't believe the Buggy Pirates
were defeated by Betty Thieves.
We aren't petty thieves.
We're pirates.
Luke, I'm going to sleep. Good.
I'm looking forward to this.
You guys are pirates?
Yeah, we're searching for the Grand Line.
Ha!
That's not an easy voyage, you know,
and I don't think that two halfwits
the likes of you can handle it.
And what will you do if by some
miracle you manage to make it there?
Go on a sightseeing tour or something?
Be king of the pirates!
You can't be serious, you idiot!
If you were king of the pirates,
then that would make me God!
God,
there's only one who can be king of the
pirates and obtain all
this world's treasures,
and that's gonna be me, you got it?
You're annoying.
Let's go ahead and settle this.
Seeing that Straw Hat
brings back memories of him,
and that really gets my blood boiling.
So bring it on, you wanted a pirate.
You remind me of him.
That damn cheeky red-haired pirate.
What did you say?
The red hair.
Wait, are you saying you
knew my old friend, Shanks?
That's right.
I knew Shanks once.
Do you know where he is now?
I don't know.
I guess that depends, Straw Hat.
Maybe I do, and maybe I don't.
What are you talking about?
Did you forget?
No, I didn't forget, you moron!
But I'm not just going to tell you where
he is out of the kindness of my heart.
You have to work for that info.
Fine, I'll make you tell me.
You can give it your best shot,
but I don't like your chances.
I doubt Rubber can
bounce back from a blade.
You're right.
Chop, chop! Ricecracker!
Can't move in mid-air, can you? Too bad.
No, you're wrong!
Oh, how interesting.
You're not so bad either, but
here comes Gum-Gum Hissle!
Their neat abilities, all right,
but they leave you wide open.
I'll carve you up! Gum-Gum!
Jump, jump, quick escape! Hissle!
Not good enough, Gum-Gum.
Damn, you keep breaking into pieces. What?
They're still going at it?
I can't believe these guys.
Uh, hey, did you see that?
You dumbass.
Pretend you're still knocked out.
If you get yourself caught
in the middle of that,
then there's no way you'll
ever make it out alive.
Chop, chop, cannon!
Separate.
So, Rutt, you want to give up yet?
You bastard! How's that?
Was I not supposed to scratch
your face or something?
Bastard!
No one damages my lucky hat
and walks away from it alive!
This hat is my only treasure!
And anyone who so much as lays
a finger on it is going to pay!
Yeah, I made a solemn promise.
I promised the guy who
gave me this hat that I'd
form a crew and become
the greatest pirate ever.
And I didn't think that there
was anything that could faze him.
But look at him.
He's getting so upset about a hat.
Hmm, it seems that hat has a
history to it. That's right!
Is it really all that special?
If that's the case, you should protect it!
I'll leave this hat to you.
It means more to me than anything in the
world, so you better take good care of it.
You hear me?
I want you to bring this hat back
to me someday, in good condition.
And only once you've
become a great pirate.
That's our promise, Luffy.
You really consider this worthless
dirty Straw Hat a treasure?
You need to grow up, boy!
Shut up!
When Shanks gave me
that, I made a promise!
What?
So you're telling me that
this used to be Shanks' hat?
No wonder it looked so familiar.
He always wore it when I knew him.
So you and Shanks were members
of the same pirate crew?
Yeah.
Back when we were pirates in
training, we were fellow comrades.
That damn detestable,
red-haired, Blackford!
Shanks is a much better
man than you'll ever be!
You don't have the right to call him comrade,
and don't you ever badmouth him again!
Time for my chop-chop quick escape!
I don't want you to ever mention
Shakes' name to me again, you bastard!
I can see whatever the
hell I want about Shakes.
Tell me what happened between you and
Shakes and where can I find him now?
Damn it how dare you tear
up my treasured Straw Hat!
Do you really want to
know he's the one person
that I loathe I'll curse
his name for the rest?
of my life, as long as there's
breath in my body, Shanks,
I will never forgive you.
That place before someone could beat me,
the promised land was in my grasp
and I wouldn't let
Go my only dream,
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true
But if the world ever changes,
I call out your name We could return
to the time when everything's the same
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade
Waiting for that one true dream?
We'll be back.